Nancy W. Anderson Papers MS112
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Publications and press, 1940 -- 1995; MS112.006; 1.2 Linear Feet
  - Freshwater Wetlands, Their Nature and Importance to Man, by Norton H. Nickerson, 1978; MS112.006.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Georges Bank Marine Sanctuary Issue Paper, by Office of Coastal Zone Management and the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 1979; MS112.006.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - I Dare You, by William H. Denforth, 1940; MS112.006.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Lincoln Filene Center for Citizenship and Public Affairs pamphlets, 1982 -- 1983; MS112.006.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Long Inter-basin Diversions or Transfers of Water, Speech, by Nancy Anderson, MS112.006.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - National Workshop on Environmental Education and Networking, Machakos, Kenya, Draft Report, compiled by Samina R. Khan, 1995; MS112.006.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - NEEC New England Environmental Conference, 1979 -- 1983; MS112.006.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - NEEN Appendix for the Final Report, 1977 -- 1978; MS112.006.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Networking in Environmental Education, EAEN Workshop, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, 1995; MS112.006.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Poster for Public Meeting, Role of Local Conservation Commissions, Gloucester, Massachusetts, 1982; MS112.006.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - President's Council on Sustainable Development Seventh Meeting, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1994; MS112.006.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Proceedings from the Second Annual Growth Management Forum, Sustaining the Economic and Environmental Future of New England, 1990; MS112.006.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Proposal for a New England Environmental Leadership Renewal Program, Lincoln Filene Center for Citizenship and Public Affairs, 1983; MS112.006.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Proposed Wetlands Protection District, Conservation Commission, Reading, Massachusetts, 1975; MS112.006.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Public Response to the President's Council on Sustainable Development, Draft Vision Statement and Principles for Sustainable Development, Executive Summary, prepared by Dinah Bear, MS112.006.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Reading Conservation Plan, 1976; MS112.006.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Report, Assessing Practices Committee, Town of Reading, Special Town Meeting, 1970; MS112.006.002.00043 (Box 2)
    November 16
  - Summary of the Proceedings for Achieving Sustainable Development in New England, 1995; MS112.006.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Sustainability, It Has to Come From Two Sides, by Frits Hesselink, 1990; MS112.006.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - The Taproot of Environmental and Development Crisis in Africa, the Great Challenge, by J. J. Otim, 1992; MS112.006.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Third Annual Earth Week Inner City Environmental Conference, Dorchester, Massachusetts, 1977; MS112.006.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - UNCED Declaration, Rio Declaration on Environment and Development, 1992; MS112.006.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - Update, Lincoln Filene Center for Citizenship and Public Affairs, 1981; MS112.006.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - What on Earth, WGBY Newsletter, 1990; MS112.006.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - Worldwatch papers, 1976 -- 1992; MS112.006.002.00051 (Box 2)
- Visual materials, 1981 -- 1997; MS112.007; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains un-filed photos, slides, negative proofs, and a video. There were two photo albums with pictures from the EAEN conference in 1994. Most other photographs and negatives were found in envelopes, sometimes dated but unlabeled. Photos found loose in boxes were put in a folder titled "Miscellaneous Photographs."
  One group of labeled slides was taken in Yerevan, USSR, 1989. One group of slides was unlabeled but presumably taken in the Indian sub-continent. One carrel of slides was labeled "Africa Show." The second carrel of slides was unlabeled but was presumably taken in Africa. Total number of slides: 256.
  The video is from the University of Southern Maine and is titled "Senior College U.S.M. 3-4/97."
  This series is arranged loosely chronologically.
  - Photo proofs, negatives NEEC, 1981; MS112.007.001.00017 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Photo Nancy Anderson, 1981; MS112.007.001.00018 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Photos NEEC, 1986; MS112.007.001.00019 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Photos, proofs, negatives - Globescope, 1986; MS112.007.001.00020 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Photos Globescope, 1986 -- 1992; MS112.007.001.00021 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
    Includes NEEN 1992
  - Photos NEEN, 1991; MS112.007.001.00022 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Photo proofs NEEC, 1991; MS112.007.001.00023 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Photos Nancy Anderson, 1992; MS112.007.001.00024 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Photo proofs, negatives Nancy Anderson, 1992; MS112.007.001.00025 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - EAEN conference photo album (1), 1994; MS112.007.001.00026 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - EAEN conference photo album (2), 1994; MS112.007.001.00027 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Miscellaneous photos, MS112.007.001.00028 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
    Photos found un-filed. No Date Available
  - Photos, proofs NEEC, MS112.007.001.00029 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Photo proofs, negatives, MS112.007.001.00030 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Slides: Yerevan, 'Africa Show', Africa, MS112.007.001.00031 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
    Slide box contains slides 1-202. No Date Available
  - Slides: India (?), MS112.007.001.00032 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
  - Slides: India (?), MS112.007.001.00033 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
    Slide box contains slides 237-256. No Date Available
  - Video: Senior College USM, 1997-03; MS112.007.001.00034 (Box MS112 Shared 1)
    videocassette